Guide to the Shayle Searle papers, 1963-1994.
Searle, Shayle papers, 1963-1994.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Shayle Searle papers, 1963-1994.
21-40-3200.
S. R. (Shayle R.) Searle, 1928-.
2.4 cubic feet.
Teaching and course materials, assignments, examinations.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Course material on Statistics and Matrix Algebra courses taught by Professor Searle.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Biometrics, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Course material on Statistics and Matrix Algebra courses taught by Professor Searle.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Searle, S. R. 1928-.; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Biometry--Study and teaching.; Statistics.; Matrices.; Biomathematics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
  - Matrix Algebra - Statistics- 416/417, 1980's-1990's (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - Statistics 417 - Assignments, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Statistics 417 - Prelims, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Statistics 417 - Prelims, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Statistics 417 - Prelims, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Statistics 417 - Final Exams, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Statistics 417 - Final Exams, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Statistics 417 - Final Exams, 1963-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Technical Reports, 1962-2000 (Box 2)
    Bu73 - Bu876, Bu150M - Bu1590M
  - Technical Reports & Articles, 1970's-1990's (Box 3)
    Course material, reviews of articles, correspondence